empowerednews.net 2018-09-27

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**What information do we collect?**

EmpoweredNews (empowerednews.net) collects information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website ( we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer

  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

**Note** : If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

For a video about cookies visit [www.google.com/goodtoknow/data-on-the-web/cookies](https://www.google.com/goodtoknow/data-on-the-web/cookies).

EmpoweredNews uses analytics data and the DoubleClick cookie to serve ads (Display Advertising) based on a user's prior visits to our website (Remarketing).  Site visitors may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Google advertising opt-out page") or they may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout "Google Analytics opt-out page").

Google has additional information available about their [Remarketing Privacy Guidelines](https://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=100746 "Google's Remarketing Privacy Guidelines"), [Policies](https://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=143465 "Google's Remarketing Policies"), and [Restrictions](https://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=178363 "Google's Remarketing Privacy Restrictions").

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, EmpoweredNews has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we well post those changes on this page

This policy was last modified on December 26, 2012

**Contacting us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the Contact page
